export const data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Footprinting and Reconnaissance",
    answer:
      "We gather critical information about your target systems and organization, mapping network infrastructure and identifying potential vulnerabilities. Our comprehensive reconnaissance techniques enable us to build a detailed understanding of your security landscape.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Scanning Networks",
    answer:
      "Our experts utilize cutting-edge scanning tools to identify active hosts, open ports, and services running on your network. Through meticulous network scanning and mapping, we uncover potential weaknesses and vulnerabilities that could be exploited by attackers.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Enumeration",
    answer:
      "We conduct thorough enumeration to extract valuable information about user accounts, network resources, and services. Our detailed enumeration process helps us identify any weak configurations or system vulnerabilities that may exist within your infrastructure.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "System Hacking",
    answer:
      "With our in-depth knowledge of hacking techniques, we can assess your systems for potential unauthorized access points. By simulating real-world attack scenarios, we help you identify and address vulnerabilities, including password cracking, privilege escalation, and backdoor attacks.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Malware Threats",
    answer:
      "Our team specializes in analyzing and mitigating malware threats. We employ advanced tools and techniques to detect, analyze, and remove various types of malware, including viruses, worms, Trojans, ransomware, and spyware.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Sniffing and Traffic Analysis",
    answer:
      " Through network traffic analysis, we detect and prevent unauthorized interception of sensitive data. By implementing robust sniffing countermeasures, we protect against data breaches and ensure the confidentiality of your network traffic.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Social Engineering Assessments",
    answer:
      " We conduct social engineering assessments to test your organization's resilience against human vulnerabilities. By simulating real-world scenarios, we help you identify weaknesses in employee awareness and implement effective training programs to mitigate the risk of social engineering attacks.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Web Application Security",
    answer:
      "Our experts assess and secure your web applications against common vulnerabilities, such as SQL injection, cross-site scripting (XSS), and cross-site request forgery (CSRF). We employ best practices and advanced tools to protect your web applications from potential attacks.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Wireless Network Security",
    answer:
      "With the growing prevalence of wireless networks, we ensure your wireless infrastructure is secure. We conduct thorough assessments to identify and mitigate vulnerabilities, including Wi-Fi hacking, rogue access points, and encryption weaknesses.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Cryptography",
    answer:
      "Our team provides expert guidance on encryption algorithms, secure key management, digital signatures, and cryptographic protocols. We ensure your cryptographic implementations are robust and resistant to attacks.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Intrusion Detection and Prevention",
    answer:
      " We help you establish effective intrusion detection and prevention systems (IDS/IPS) to detect and mitigate potential threats. Our experts ensure that your systems are equipped to identify and respond to suspicious activities promptly.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Penetration Testing",
    answer:
      "Our certified ethical hackers perform comprehensive penetration tests to identify vulnerabilities in your systems and networks. We simulate real-world attacks to test your defenses and provide detailed reports with actionable recommendations for enhancing your security posture.",
  },
];
